This is...
an abandoned tile.
I bought it.
I plan to open
an immersive themes of calligraphy and painting.
This is the reason
with Mr. Chu.
Theater.
The main plot of Mo Xiang
the male and female lead
opened a calligraphy shop.
I'll upgrade it for you.
Yes.
Can you and Sis Wan say you can draw?
We can make a stage play
a stage play.
With my excellent acting skills,
and passerby,
you will definitely get a lot of fans.
There will be no empty seats.
Then the money...
Nonsense.
You're a noble lady.
How can you hang out
with a man like him?
I need to speed up the main plot.
Don't bother.
Keying.
Are you short of money these days?
No.
I'm thinking about your future.
Think about it.
When you have money and career,
you can get out of the cage
and live independently.
and live
your own life.
Miss Ke Ying is right.
Sister Wan.
You don't have to be
in the mansion.
can fly out of the house
and do what you want to do.
As expected of the male lead.
The view and values
are different.
A scholar like you
can only talk big.
A person's identity and fate
can be changed easily?
With money and talent,
can survive
in this world?
I'll crush you to death.
It's as simple as
to kill an ant.
Young Master Ning is right.
It’s hard to change your fate against heaven.
After all, crickets can't shake the tree.
But if a person
If it's just a fate
I never try my best
What's the difference
is no different from death.
Keying's idea is good.
Count me in.
You finally figured it out.
Great.
I didn't expect a daughter like you
know the secret passage
behind the fake mountain.
I know a lot.
Let's go.
Looks like your leg hasn't recovered.
Why are you here?
I...
Looks like your leg has recovered.
You kept lying to me.
and took your sister out in the middle of the night.
How dare you!
Father, you misunderstood.
Ying'er, shut up!
Let's go.
Lan.
Stay still.
Go forward.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Xiaolan told me
you met Chu Qingjun
at Magpie Bridge.
Is it true?
I did meet Mr. Chu.
So what?
Chu Qingjun is just a painter.
You are going to get married.
but you secretly met a man.
If Ning Yuanyan knows,
I will be humiliated.
Mr. Chu is from a well-educated family.
Why don’t you help him and my sister?
I can handle
Ning Yuanzhi.
I've taught you since you were little.
I thought you were the most obedient and obedient.
But now you're lying.
You even deceived your father.
Why did I go out late at night?
Is it safe?
Why do I keep pretending to be crippled?
I didn't ask anything.
He only cares about his dignity.
Do you really want to
to force me
forced me to die.
will I be humiliated?
You disloyal and unfilial daughter!
How dare you!
I didn’t mean it.
to marry my sister.
She's just holding you hostage
to control you.
Please decide
Please decide.
Cancel the engagement.
Nonsense.
Don't I know that?
His Majesty's order
is testing me
to break off the engagement.
is against His Majesty.
Ying.
I've warned you
not to contact Ning Yuan Ci.
Nothing he said
is true.
He wants to control you.
and stabilize the morale of the army.
It's enough
is enough.
Stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
It's just acting.
It's common to get slapped.
It's nothing.
is nothing.
Don't move.
I don't understand.
why father insisted
to marry you to Ning Yuan Ci?
My mother and I
were not favored by him.
When my mother passed away,
not only did he not shed a single tear,
He even
burned her belongings.
To him,
for him.
is to marry
a powerful man.
Even his biological father
I have no right
to take away your freedom.
and use you as a tool.
Don't give in.
Freedom.
A woman like me
like me,
I'm afraid
that I can't even imagine.
Don't think like that.
Freedom and dreams
are not something you can easily get.
We have to overcome all difficulties
and fight for it.
Fly bravely.
I will help you.
How do you have
the key to the warehouse?
My mother's special tea.
so that my father
right now.
I have no choice.
My mother loves me so much.
Stealing money from the warehouse
to steal money from the warehouse.
Money is the most important thing in business.
If you don't take it from home,
Should I steal it from outside?
Besides,
Father made Chu Qingjun lose his position
in the palace
and cut off his life.
We should
as soon as possible
to help him.
So much gold and silver.
Just a little bit. No one will notice.
This painting is so exquisite.
Isn't it valuable?
It's indeed a good painting.
From the pencil technique
and the characteristics
are all like everyone.
but they may not be valuable.
Forget it if you can't sell it.
I think jewelry is better.
Xue Ruowan and Chu Qingjun.
Both of them
One is not in love,
One has no mouth
causing the relationship to develop too slowly.
Fortunately, with money,
I can
develop my career line in advance.
and have the chance to spend time with each other.
Two people
have to make some sparks.
But the biggest problem now
is this couple.
They refuse to give up the engagement.
I'll always be stuck in the first test.
What should I do?
When you kissed me last time,
you didn't get my permission.
Last time,
When?
Right here.
Last Qixi Festival,
If Ning Yuan
just
using Xue Keying.
[How did she spend her first kiss]
and location
and location.
It seems that
a hypocrite
but he's so pure and arrogant.
If
he really has feelings for Xue Keying,
Then I have an idea.
Lan.
Xue Ruowan's painting
the burned Phoenix Nirvana
Where did it go?
I can't find him anywhere.
I was going to
to find Chu Qingjun.
Take a look.
Maybe she
put it away herself.
I don't know.
Lan
has shown her hostility
on my face.
You didn't even pretend.
It's exactly the same
when I entered the industry.
The weasel greets the chicken.
That painting
was broken
by them.
I must hide the painting.
I can't let her find it again.
She is grounded at home.
But she seduced Mr. Chu
to seduce Mr. Chu.
What a bad woman.
General Ning is here.
What did you call me?
General Ning.
have always looked down on
these brothels.
Why are you here today?
I suspect that at the Qixi Lantern Festival,
who fought with Cui Hu
is an enemy detective from the North.
This man
hiding in the city.
You are the manager here.
You should know
Don't let the thief in.
Otherwise,
you can't bear
You can't afford it.